Register of the Russia. Missiia (Norway) Records, 1781-1924
Hoover Institution Archives
- VITSE-KONSUL'STVO, BERGEN
  - Correspondence
    - 1919
      - Danishevskii, P. (Box 117., Folder 1)
      - Shipping
        - SS"Antonii" (Folder 2)
        - SS"Ivan Susanin" (Folder 3)
        - SS"Sever" (Folder 4)
    - 1920
      - General (Folder 5-7)
      - Gran, H. (Folder 8)
      - Severnaia Oblast', commercial activity (Folder 9)
  - Commercial contracts
    - 1900-1907 (Folder 10)
    - 1914 (Folder 11)
    - 1916 (Folder 12)
  - Personal certificates, mostly Finnish sailors, 1917-1919 (Folder 12-16)
  - Questionnaires, Torneo Border Station. Includes visas and other documents issued by Provisional Government and Soviet authorities in Murmansk, 1917-1921 (Box 118., Folder 1-10)
    - Wills, 1917-1918 (Folder 11)
- VITSE-KONSUL'STVO, KRISTIANSUND
  - Correspondence with Konsul'stvo, Kristiania, 1882-1913 (Box 118., Folder 12)
  - Consular instructions (Folder 13)
- VITSE-KONSUL'STVO, MANDAL'
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1888-1913 (Box 119., Folder 1)
    - Konsul'stvo, Kristiania
      - 1881-1882 (Folder 2)
      - 1886 (Folder 3)
      - 1887-1888 (Folder 4)
      - 1892-1900 (Folder 5)
      - 1900-1905 (Folder 6)
      - 1906-1913 (Folder 7)
  - Official regulations and instructions from Russian Foreign Ministry to Russian Consulates abroad, 1878-1913 (Folder 8-9)
    - Record book, bound, 1880-1909 (Folder 10)
- VITSE-KONSUL'STVO, STAVANGER
  - Correspondence, Konsul'stvo Kristiania, 1857-1910 (Box 120., Folder 1-2)
  - Official regulations and instructions from Russian Foreign Ministry to Russian Consulates abroad, 1816-1913 (Folder 3)
- VITSE-KONSUL'STVO, TONSBERG
  - Register, bound, 1876-1913 (Box 120., Folder 4)
  - Official regulations and instructions, from Russian Foreign Ministry to Russian Consulates abroad, 1860 (Folder 5)
- VITSE-KONSUL'STVO, TRONDHJEM
  - Correspondence, including Konsul'stvo Kristiania
    - 1914-1916 (Box 120., Folder 6)
    - 1915-1917, bound (Folder 7)
    - 1916-1917, in alphabetical order (Folder 8-12)
    - 1917-1918, bound (Box 121., Folder 1)
    - 1917 (Folder 2)
    - 1918 (Folder 3)
    - 1919 (Folder 4-6)
    - 1920 (Box 122., Folder 1-3)
    - 1921 (Folder 4-5)
    - 1922 (Folder 6)
- VOENNYI AGENT
  - IUdenich, Gen.-of-Infantry, miscellaneous material by and about him also Gen. Bulakh-Balakhovich, typescript copies, 1920 (Box 123., Folder 1)
  - Palen, Countess Ol'ga, article re imprisonment of Imperial Family (Folder 2)
  - Reports
    - General, re conditions in Soviet Union, especially northern sector, 1920 (Folder 3-8)
      - Voennyi Agent v Danii to Lieut.-Gen. E. Miller, 1919-1920 (Folder 9-11)
    - Excerpts from foreign press, 1920, miscellaneous (Folder 12-14)
- VOENNO-MORSKOI AGENT
  - Gidrograficheskoe sudno "Vakan", miscellaneous material, 1918-1920 (Box 124., Folder 1)
  - Voenno-Morskoe Vedomstvo, miscellaneous material, especially re Morskie Sily Severnoi Oblasti, includes correspondence of Lieut.-Gen. E. Miller, 1919-1920 (Folder 2)
  - Naval personnel
    - Arkhangel'skii flotskii poluekipazh, list of officers and men, 1916-1917 (Folder 3)
      - List of disbanded naval personnel, 1918 (Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous material, especially re disbanding of fleet and refugee status of personnel, 1919-1920 (Folder 5-6)
- MISSIIA (SWEDEN)
  - Reports and correspondence
    - 1895 (Box 127., Folder 1)
    - 1896 (Folder 2)
    - 1899 (Folder 3)
    - 1900 (Folder 4)
    - 1901 (Folder 5)
    - 1902 (Folder 6)
    - 1903 (Folder 7)
    - 1904 (Folder 8)
    - 1905 (Folder 9)
  - Lapps
    - 1896 (Folder 10)
    - 1897 (Folder 11)
    - 1898 (Folder 12)
    - 1899 (Folder 13)
    - 1900 (Folder 14)
    - 1904 (Folder 15)
    - 1905 (Folder 16)
  - Spitzbergen, 1896-1901 (Folder 17)
- OVERSIZE FILE
  - Konsul'stvo, Christianiia (Box 129.)
    - Documents issued, bound books
      - 1910
      - 1911
      - 1912
      - 1913
    - Poster describing official stamp tariff, n.d.
    - Stamp tariff, bound record file
      - 1912
      - 1913
      - 1913-1919
      - 1915
  - Vitse-konsul'stvo, Bergen (Box 130.)
    - Bound contracts, 1914
    - Consular stamps, record book of disbursements, 1915-1918
    - Correspondence, incoming, mostly Russian Mission in Christianiia, bound, 1916
    - Financial records, bound file, 1916-1917